#### **OBJECTIVE: DATA ANALYST**

Former Graphic Designer & Operations Manager transitioning into a **Data Analyst** role. Looking to take advantage of my skills in graphic design over 5 years of experience for more effective and efficient data visualizations and communications. **Key skills include:** 

Data Visualization

Data Modeling

Communication

Research

Relational Databases

Project Management

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

• University of California, Irvine – Division of Continuing Education – Data Science Certificate (2021) (8 months, 150 hours of evaluated learning) (4.0 GPA)

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Data Science : SQL, Tableau, Python, KNIME, RapidMiner and Excel.

Web Development : HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Node.JS.
Graphic Design : Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign.

#### **LINKS**

- <u>Portfolio Website</u> Portfolio website with a brief introduction about myself.
- Tableau Dashboard Tableau Public dashboard that showcases my recent projects.
- GitHub GitHub repositories that showcases my other data science projects.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **IKEDA Japanese Dining**

#### **Huntington Beach, CA**

## Graphic Designer and Operations Manager

2020 - 2021

- Coordinated employee work schedules and performed all administrative works.
- Implemented and executed all graphic design needs such as new menu design and advertisements.

## WeGen Solar Inc. Fullerton, CA

## **Graphic Designer and Operations Manager**

2015 - 2020

- In charge of interconnection process for solar commercial and residential projects.
- Managed solar monitoring system maintenances for commercial solar projects and all residential customers.
- In charge of every graphic design work for marketing purposes (advertisements and sales support).

## SuperCap Co. Los Angeles, CA

# Co-Founder and Online Marketing Manager

2014 - 2014

- Co-founded a hat retail company and performed as an online marketing manager.
- Increased sales by creating an official company website with WordPress and selling products online via company website and eBay.
- Raised brand awareness by advertising and managing online product campaigns.

#### **CJ Entertainment America Inc.**

Los Angeles, CA

# Temporary Graphic Designer in Marketing Team

2013 - 2014

- Responsible for daily graphic design needs and video editing for Korean films and corporate events.
- Wrote newly released Asian film press kits and shared with US film media and critics.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Purdue University, College of Technology**

West Lafayette, IN

Bachelor of Science | Computer Graphics Technology

May 2013